Inventory of the Jonathan Boucher Papers, 1759-1803
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Boucher to Sir Frederick Morton Eden [1766-1809; D.N.B.; son of Sir Robert Eden, former Governor of Maryland; author of The State of the Poor.], (A/3).
  - J[onathan] B[oucher] to Sir Fred[erick] M[orton] Eden n.d. Wed A.M., 1 p. ALS. (A/3/18). (Box-folder 1:16)
    He is in poor health, with rheumatism, a headache and a slight fever.
  - J[onathan] B[oucher] to Sir F[rederik Morton] Eden n.d. Thursday A.M., 1 p. ALS. (A/3/19). (Box-folder 1:16)
    He thanks Eden for his kind hospitality. He intends to write a tactful letter to Lady Eden [Sir Frederick's mother].
- Boucher to ?William Knox [D.N.B.; Undersecretary of State for America]
  - Jonathan Boucher to William Knox (?) 27 Nov. 1775, Copy letter. The original was formerly in the Stopford Sackville collection, H.M.C. Stopford Sackville II, 19-20; now at William L. Clements Library, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 8 pp. CY of ALS. (A/4/1). (Box-folder 1:17)
    There is a principle of revolt in all colonies which stems from a lack of foresight in colony administration; the subduing of the rebellion in America is of secondary importance to the new-modelling of its Government. Says focus of the war should be placed on New England. Decisive action against Washington is imperative to the British cause. New York is well- disposed and would make a good base for the King's troops. Advocates control of New York from New York City to Albany to split the northern colonies from the southern. Pennsylvania has made no overt act of treason nor raised any troops; the Carolinias, Virginia and Maryland are too busy with internal problems, i.e. Indians and slaves, to seek regular troops in a hostile way; the white servants would certainly enlist with the King's troops, Baltimore and Annapolis contain many such men; trade embargos should be sufficient to deal with these colonies. Washington shows extraordinary coolness and caution but has very little personal experience; the first general action against him must be decisive.
- Letters from the Rev. Jonathan Boucher to William Eden [D.N.B., Undersecretary of State]
  - [Rev] Jonathan Boucher, Paddington, [Eng.] to W[illia]m Eden, Undersecretary of State 27 June 1776, Copy; original in Public Record Office. 4 pp. CY of ALS. (A/4/2a). (Box-folder 1:18)
    As it is difficult for a gentleman who has been used to better circumstances to learn to live on £70 p.a., he solicits Eden's good offices with Lord George [Germain] for a further supply of money. He claims no special merit for his actions in America, but others who have done less have received pensions. He would like to be commended to Lord Dartmouth, the Abp. of Canterbury and the Bps. of London and Bangor, and hopes that Eden may be able to help him to preferment in America when a settlement is reached.
- Letters from William Eden to Mr. Pownall, Secretary to Board of Trade
  - W[illia]m Eden, Downing Street, [London, Eng.] to Mr. Pownall, Secretary to Board of Trade 4 July 1776, Copy; original in Public Record Office. 2 pp. CY of ALS. (A/4/2b). (Box-folder 1:19)
    He encloses Boucher's letter and recommends that something be done for him. He wishes one of the King's ships on the Southern Station to be directed to call in at Annapolis to take letters to his brother [Robert Eden, Governor of Maryland].
- Letters from he Rev. Jonathan Boucher to Elizabeth Hodgson [see family table]
  - Jona[tha]n Boucher, Paddington, [Eng.], to Elizabeth Hodgson 28 Febr[ua]ry 1784, 3 pp. ALS. (A/4/3). (Box-folder 1:20)
    He offers her re-assurance and encouragement on her forthcoming marriage to his friend [John James, the younger], and assures her that she will find herself among friends in his house.
- Letters from the Rev. Jonathan Boucher to Dr. John Douglas, Bp. of Salisbury [D.N.B.]
  - Jonathan Boucher, Epsom, [Eng.] to Dr. John Douglas, Bishop of Salisbury, [London, Eng.] 9 Feb. 1800, Copy; orig. in B.M., Egerton MSS. 2186 f. 110. 4 pp. CY of ALS. (A/4a). (Box-folder 1:21)
    He has declined position of Principal Minister of the English Episcopal Chapel in Edinburgh because the Scottish Anglicans refuse to render obedience to the Scottish bishops; he asks the Bishop to assist the cause of Scottish Union which he has so long supported. Edinburgh is captivated with popular preaching; even Bp. Abernethy Drummond stipulates that the English assistant he requires must be a good preacher. Cautioned Bp. Drummond to be cautious in his choice because his mitre might well come down to his chosen person.
  - Jonathan Boucher, Epsom, [Eng.] to Dr. John Douglas, Bishop of Salisbury, London, [Eng.] 26 Feb. 1800, Copy; original in British Museum, Egerton MSS. 2186 f. 112. 5 pp. CY of ALS. (A/4b). (Box-folder 1:21)
    He does not expect Douglas, in his present state of health, to play any active part in promoting Scottish Union, but he might certainly use his influence to remove prejudice. He has advised Bp. Drummond, who is apt to be intemperate in his zeal, and Bp. Skinner [of Aberdeen] to write an address to the English Bishops, and he suggests that Douglas should write to the Episcopal Congregations of Edinburgh. The obstacle of the Abjuration Oath will soon be removed as it will doubtless be repealed on the death of the Cardinal of New York, which may be daily expected.
- Letters to the Rev. Jonathan Boucher from the Rev. James Maury [educated William and Mary College, Virginia; tutor to Thomas Jefferson; died 1769.]
  - James Maury, Frederi[ck]sville Parish, Albemarle County, [Va.], to Jonathan Boucher [15 April 1763], Letter mounted on paper with pencil notes including passage on friendship from letter of 20 Feb., 1764, not in this collection. Medium oversize file. (B/1/1). (Box-folder 2:1)
    As mutual friends give him a good account of Boucher's taste, openness of temper and goodness of heart, and he has seen and admired part of a letter written to Mr. Tickell [see Boucher letters to Tickell], he is eager to be placed among his correspondents and friends.
  - [James Maury], Albemarle [Co.], [Va.], to [Jonathan] Boucher 22 Nov. 1763, 7 pp. AL. (B/1/2). (Box-folder 2:1)
    Detailed consideration of a poetical letter by Boucher which is to published by Royle; Boreas Self bowing to publish an article through the Maryland Gazette which vindicated the Virginia House of Burgesses voting an award of £2500 to Mr. Randolph for defending the House's opposition to the Governor's demand for a pistole for every land patent he signed because the Virginia presses did not wish to offend the Governor and his council. Boucher need not fear to be discovered as the author, as it will recommend him to the most sensible, equitable, and honest part of the Clergy and Laity. Maury comments extensively on his regard for Boucher. Boucher should get Mr. Jackson's opinion of the work. Tickell is to accompany Maury to Hanover Court where his case is to be heard.
  - Narrative of the determination of a suit between the Minister of Fredericksville, plaintiff, and the collectors of the said parish, defendants, for arrears of salary, in Hanover Court, November and December 1763 n.d. [1763?], In the hand of the Rev. James Maury. AMS. (B/1/3). (Box-folder 2:1)
    [In 1760, the Crown had disallowed an Act passed by the Virginia Assembly to prevent clergy of the Established Church, whose salaries had hitherto been calculated in tobacco, from profiting by a heavy rise in its price. Patrick Henry began his political career by opposing Maury's claim for arrears in the "Parson's Cause".] The jury was not of persons of rank and understanding, and although the verdict was in favour of the plaintiff, only one penny damages was awarded; the Jury had been harangued by one of the Defendant's lawyers [Patrick Henry] who asserted "that the King, by annulling and disallowing laws of so salutary a nature [the Two Penny Act of 1758], from being the Father of his people, degenerates into a tyrant and forfeits all right to his subjects' obedience;" at which there were cries of Treason! The road to popularity here is to trample underfoot the Interests of Religion, the Rights of the Church, and the Prorogative of the Crown.
  - James Maury to [Jonathan] Boucher 7 July 1764, 4 pp. ALS. (B/1/4). (Box-folder 2:2)
    He apologizes for not having written since he had the pleasure of seeing Boucher. The death of Mr. [Robert] Jackson is their common loss. He hears Boucher is taking on the glebe of St. Mary's, and wishes him success. Comments that he thinks Boucher told him his sister is living with him.
  - [James] Maury, Albemarle [Co., Va.], to [Jonathan] Boucher 30 Aug[ust] 1764, 4 pp. ALS. (B/1/5). (Box-folder 2:2)
    He asks Boucher to make some inquiries on his behalf to help him recover a debt for an old friend of his. He apologizes for defects in the composition of his letters, saying he writes "piping hot from the heart." Tickell is travelling in Carolina; Maury is considering moving there, but awaits information from Tickell about patronage, salaries, etc.
  - [James] Maury, Albemarle [Co., Va.], to [Jonathan] Boucher 1 Mar[ch] 1766, 4 pp. ALS. (B/1/6). (Box-folder 2:2)
    He thanks Boucher for his friendly injunctions to take care of his health, and for the help he has given him in correcting his verses. His son will not be able to assist Boucher in his school as he intends to go to Carolina with his father.
  - [James] Maury to [Jonathan] Boucher 3 Oct[ober] 1767, 1 p. ALS. (B/1/7). (Box-folder 2:2)
    He has answered Boucher's enquiries with regard to Mr. Messenger in a previous letter. Tickell has long since returned but he has not seen or heard from him. He urges Boucher to visit him.
  - [James] Maury, Fred[ericks]ville [Parish, Albemarle County, Va.], to [Jonathan] Boucher 25 Nov[embe]r 1767, 1 p. ALS. (B/1/8). (Box-folder 2:2)
    He has been ill since returning from his journey. He returns some papers which Boucher lent him and sends some of his own for Boucher's use.
  - J[ames] Maury, Albemarle [Co., Va.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 29 Aug[ust] 1768, 2 pp. ALS. (B/1/9). (Box-folder 2:3)
    Tickell will attend the Treaty at Chiswell's mines with Boucher, if possible; the Indians may, however, insist on the Commissioners meeting them around the boundaries of the lands to be sold. Maury has been asked to preach in a remote corner of his parish to some of his parishioners who "are perpetually attacked by Childs [or Chiles] and his brother enthusiasts." He asks Boucher to return the sermon he lent to him.
  - [James] Maury to [Jonathan] Boucher [19 Dec. 1768], 3 pp. ALS. (B/1/10). (Box-folder 2:3)
    As an administrator, Boucher should know that, shortly before his death, Tickell sold a quantity of rum to Mr. Lewis, one half of which Maury bought; he paid Lewis, so Lewis should have settled for the whole. Maury asks Boucher to bid for Clarke's Sermons at the sale of Tickell's books. He is not optimistic about his chances of being appointed to Trinity Parish [?Louisa County - Tickell parish].
  - [James Maury] to [Jonathan] Boucher, Caroline [Co., Va.] 19 Dec. 1768, 2 pp. ADS. (B/1/11). (Box-folder 2:3)
    A list of books for which Maury wishes Boucher to send to Glasgow; religious works, Italian Grammar, Blackstone's Commentaries, Tristram Shandy and The Vicar of Wakefield.
  - [James] Maury, Albemarle [Co., Va.], to Jonathan Boucher, Caroline [Co., Va.] 14 Feb[ruary] 1769, 3 pp. ALS. (B/1/12). (Box-folder 2:3)
    Asks Boucher to return a sermon on Regeneration among Tickell's papers, and a discourse by Tickell on Unity. He is drawing up an address, which he hopes to publish, to combat the Anabaptists. He is at present unwell with "the blind piles and gout."
- Letters to the Rev. Jonathan Boucher from the Rev. Myles Cooper [1737-85; President of King's College, New York; returned to England in 1775; curate of Paddington; rector of Sulhamstead.]
  - M[yles] Cooper, Kings College, New York, to [Jonathan] Boucher, Upper Marlborough, Maryland 14 June 1773, 3 pp. ALS. (B/2). (Box-folder 2:4)
    Washington has brought hm Boucher's letter; he urges him to come to New York. Mr. Custis [Washington's stepson and Boucher's former pupil] is to enjoy special privileges at King's College as he is older than the other boys. Congratulates Boucher on his victory over two lawyers. Deplores number of Dissenters in America and is glad to hear that Oxford is standing firm against them. He is looking for a place for Mr. Seabury, a worthy clergyman. A Mr. Smith of South Carolina is "pitched upon for an American Bishop."
- Letters to the Rev. Jonathan Boucher from the Rev. William Stevens [1732-1807; D.N.B.; Treasurer of Queen Anne's Bounty; biographer of Jones of Nayland.]
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.] to John [Boucher] i.e., [Jonathan Boucher] 17 May 1777, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/1). (Box-folder 2:5)
    There is to be a hurried meeting of the Committee. He has endeavored to make Boucher's peace with Dr. Glasse [Rev. Samuel Glasse; D.N.B.]. "No engagement that may not be postponed to Bishop-making."
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 17 June 1777, 1 p. ALS. singed with monogram. (B/3/2). (Box-folder 2:5)
    He attended the Committee but there was no great business.
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to Jonathan [Boucher] 12 Sept[embe]r 1777, 1 p. ALS. singed with monogram. (B/3/3). (Box-folder 2:5)
    Boucher and Mr. Addison are invited to the meeting at the Chaplain's Table tomorrow to drink Church and King like the Tories of old time.
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to Jonathan [Boucher] 24 September 1777, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/4). (Box-folder 2:5)
    He invites Boucher to Broadstreet and will advise him if he really wishes it.
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 1 Dec. 1777, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/5). (Box-folder 2:5)
    Enclosed is the fall of the Leaf [?]. Is Boucher continuing his Historico-Politico-Theological work?
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher 9 April 1778, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/6). (Box-folder 2:6)
    Stevens will call on Boucher with the Rector of Otham [his cousin, William Horne].
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to Jonathan Boucher He time is taken up by rival commitments; he wishes Boucher success with his school, and enquires after Nelly's health., 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/7). (Box-folder 2:6)
    His time is taken up by rival commitments; he wishes Boucher success with his school, and enquires after Nelly's health.
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, [London, Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 11 Nov. 1779, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/9). (Box-folder 2:6)
    Hopes to see Boucher shortly to discuss the business of his previous letter.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 22 April 1780, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/9a). (Box-folder 2:6)
    He is sorry to hear of Boucher's ill health.
  - [William Stevens] to [Jonathan] Boucher 11 Jan[uar]y 1782, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/10). (Box-folder 2:7)
    He has sent Boucher's bill for acceptance, but this cannot be done in time for his purposes. He has lent £200 to the Rector of Hanwell [Dr. Glasse]. He and Old Jones will visit Boucher on Sunday.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 17 April 1782, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/11). (Box-folder 2:7)
    He hopes to see Boucher on Friday at Bow Church. He has heard that a legacy to a refugee American clergyman by a pious lady has been disputed by her relatives [probably a reference to the legacy left to Boucher by Miss Mary Barton, the daughter of a silk merchant, who died in 1782].
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Paddington, [Eng.] 13 June 1782, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/12). (Box-folder 2:7)
    He intends to dine with Boucher on Friday.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Paddington Green, [Eng.] 26 May 1783, 2 pp. ALS. (B/3/13). (Box-folder 2:7)
    He has read the Country Curate's Letter to the Bishop of Llandaff and wishes it success. The Board [? of Queen Anne's Bounty] is to meet and he has been asked to draw up detailed accounts.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 7 July 1784, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/14). (Box-folder 2:7)
    Boucher's £100 annuity is bought for £1708 7s 6d.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Paddington Mid[dlese]x, [Eng.] 27 Aug. 1784, 2 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/15). (Box-folder 2:7)
    Stevens has visited Dr. Chandler [possibly Richard Chandler; D.N.B., classical antiquary]. Boucher is to visit Cardigan, Carmarthen and Cardiff. Stevens has not yet had Boucher's drafts accepted; he is going to Canterbury with Old Jones.
  - W[illiam] [Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 15 Sept. 1784, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/16). (Box-folder 2:8)
    He is directing this letter to Cyfarthfa where Boucher will be staying for two weeks; he hopes to see him in London on his return from Canterbury.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 26 Nov[embe]r 1784, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/17). (Box-folder 2:8)
    Murder will out! He has been charged with the authorship of the Tract.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 30 Nov[embe]r 1784, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/18). (Box-folder 2:8)
    He has been to Epsom and seen Boucher's patron and his patron's patron; he was obliged to leave Boucher's mare at Ewell.
  - [William Stevens], Broadstreet, to [Jonathan] Boucher, Paddington Green, [Eng.] 11 March 1785, 2 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/19). (Box-folder 2:8)
    He and Boucher are invited to visit Sam Glasse [Vicar of Epsom, D.N.B.] on Saturday, but as his Audit is to take place on that day, he may not be able to come.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 6 Sept[embe]r 1785, 2 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/20). (Box-folder 2:8)
    He hopes this letter does not miss Boucher at Caen [Boucher had accompanied Lord Suffield's son to Brunswick, and was returning to England with Delves, son of Sir Thomas Broughton]; Dr. Morrice [probably Secretary of the Society for the Propagation of the Gospel] feels that Boucher slighted him in not telling him about his tour till the last possible moment. Mr. Parkhurst [partron of Boucher's now living of Epsom] says that the library is ready to receive his books.
  - [William Stevens], Otham, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Caen, Normandie, [France] 12 Sep 1785, 3 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/21). (Box-folder 2:8)
    He has received Boucher's letter from Rheims; Sir Thomas Broughton has not contacted him. Dr. Morrice insists he had no wish to be rid of Boucher; he has acted only in the interests of the Society. Stevens has seen the Archbishop [of Canterbury] who has hopes that Sir Guy Carleton, the new Commander-in-Chief in America, will restore order there. The publication of Johnson's Prayers and Meditations has re-opened the question of prayers for the dead, for which Boucher once pleaded.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 9 Dec[embe]r 1785, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/22). (Box-folder 2:8)
    Stevens invites Boucher to dine with him on Monday and reminds him that he is to dine with Mr. Frere on Friday [John Frere, D.N.B., antiquary].
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to Jonathan [Boucher] 31 May 1786, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/23). (Box-folder 2:9)
    He begs to be excused the task of finding lodgings for two single ladies. He is sorry to hear of the illness of John James [see A/1/54; he died 23rd Oct. 1786]. Old Jones is to preach at Shoreditch on Tuesday. Sam Glasse expects a letter from Boucher.
  - Stevens, Otham, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 27 June 1786, 2 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/24). (Box-folder 2:9)
    He hopes Boucher managed to go to Bristol to visit the poor invalid [John James]. Darby Nyers is in financial trouble, but Stevens hopes that enough will be subscribed to avoid sequestration of his living. He invites Boucher to accompany him on a journey into Wales; he would be able to see John James again; indeed it might improve James' health to accompany them.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 25 July 1786, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/25). (Box-folder 2:9)
    Boucher's friend and companion [?] was tried at the Old Bailey. Stevens has written to Lord Dunmore [1732-1809; former Governor of New York] but he has gone to Scotland. Stevens is to visit Wales with Crawshay [probably William Crawshay, a proprietor of Cyfarthfa ironworks] and hopes to see John James at Bristol.
  - [William Stevens], Kentbury, Newbury, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Epsom, [Eng.] 10 Aug[ust] 1786, 2 pp. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/26). (Box-folder 2:9)
    He stayed a week at Cyfarthfa examining books and settling accounts [? of the ironworks]; he stayed in Bristol but had no time for visiting. The Bishop of Connecticut has written about the state of his church which Stevens termed "not at all flattering" and intends to write to Boucher.
  - [William Stevens], Otham, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 22 Sept[embe]r 1786, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/27). (Box-folder 2:9)
    Stevens and his cousin [George Horne, later Bp. of Norwich; D.N.B.] are going to Sussex for a few days but they hope to see Boucher at Otham on their return.
  - [William Stevens], Otham, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 17 June 1787, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/28). (Box-folder 2:9)
    Stevens will not side with a lady against her husband and intends to decline the Trusteeship; but Boucher, who is a kind of relation, should do what he can for her.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 2 Nov[embe]r 1787, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/29). (Box-folder 2:9)
    George Robinson [D.N.B.; bookseller] will not engage with Ogilvie [an author]. If Boucher wants a loan, it would be advisable to apply to Uncle [Charles Foreman] who would not charge interest. He hopes that Mrs. Boucher [Mary Elizabeth Foreman, died 14 Sep. 1788] is better.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 9 Feb. 1788, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/30). (Box-folder 2:10)
    He asks for details of Boucher's visit to Lambeth. Boucher would appear to have written an injudicious letter to the Bp. of Carlisle [John Douglas, later Bp. of Salisbury; D.N.B.].
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 13 Feb[ruar]y 1788, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/31). (Box-folder 2:10)
    He reassures Boucher that the Bp. of Carlisle did not resent his letter, and invites him to dine at Ewell.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher]. 26 June 1788, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/32). (Box-folder 2:10)
    He does not intend to write an answer to the recently published Vindiciae Priestlianae but recommends Boucher to do so.
  - [William Stevens], London, [Eng.], to [Jonathan Boucher] 11 July 1788, 1 p. ALS. signed with monogram. (B/3/33). (Box-folder 2:10)
    Boucher is invited to Mr. Frere's at Beddington, on his 20th wedding anniversary [John Frere was married to Jane Hookham, daughter of Steven's partner in the hosiery business]; if he comes in his carriage, Stevens will return with him to Epsom and stay till Tuesday.
  - [William Stevens], Ewell, [Eng.], to [Jonathan] Boucher, Long Town [Eng.] 4 Nov[embe]r 1788, 2 pp. ALS. (B/3/34). (Box-folder 2:10)